有多少人会来参加宝宝的欢迎会
So, what's the final head count on my baby shower?
大约有20个人  有些同事有事没空过来
About twenty. Couple people from work had something else to do.
你的妹妹们打电话来说她们没办法来
Also both of your sisters called and neither can make it.
什么  她们竟然不来参加
What? You mean they're not coming to a social event
没有男人跟酒精的社交聚会
where there's no men and no booze?
那真的是太稀奇了
That's shocking.
我不在乎  只要我妈能来就行了
I don't care, as long as my mom's here.
天啊  你妈
Oh, my God. Your mother.
怎么  我妈不会来吗
What? My mom's not gonna be here?
由于我们忘了邀请她
Well, given that we forgot to invite her,
她要是能来那还真是天大的巧合呢
it would be a big coincidence if she was.
我的天啊
My God!
不是我的错  负责邀请来宾的是菲比
It wasn't my fault, Phoebe was in charge of the invitations.
我没有妈妈  所以我常忘了
I don't have a mother. So often I forget...
少来了你
Oh, give it a rest.
所以说我妈不来参加宝宝的欢迎会吗
So my mother is not coming to my baby shower?
对
No.
我妈也不会来
Neither is mine.
你别着急
You know what? Don't worry.
我们会处理的  我们会打电话给她
We'll take care of it. We'll call her.
你先回家做准备
You go home and get ready.
确定她一定会来  这对我很重要  她是我妈
Please, make sure she comes. It's really important to me. It's my mom.
-我知道  她电话号码是多少  -我不知道
- I know. What's her number? - I don't know.
你去吧  我记在我的电话簿里了
Go. I have it in my book. Go.
等等  如果你负责邀请来宾
Wait a minute. If you're in charge of invitations,
那为什么是我打电话给她
why am I the one who has to call her?
喂  格林太太  我是莫妮卡·盖勒
Hello, Mrs. Green! Hi, it's Monica Geller.
-哈喽  莫妮卡  -嗨
- Oh, hello, Monica. - Hi.
我知道时间紧促
I know this is last-minute,
我们打算在今天临时
but we've decided to throw an impromptu...
帮瑞秋的宝宝办欢迎会
...baby shower for Rachel today.
我的女儿们已经告诉我了
I know, my daughter's told me about it
她们一个月前就接到欢迎会的"临时"请帖了
when they received their impromptu invitations a month ago.
好吧  我很抱歉
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
为什么呢  亲爱的
For what, dear?
为了没有邀请我  还是说谎骗我呢
For not inviting me, or for lying about it?
天啊  我的屁股在流汗
Oh, my God! My ass is sweating.
拜托了  您能来吗  四点开始
Please, please, can you come? It starts at 4:00.
-好吧  四点见  -谢谢
- Well, all right. I'll see you at 4. - Thank you.
-不是三点开始吗  -该死
- Isn't it at 3? - Son of a bitch!
乔伊  你要去打篮球吗
Hey, Joe! Wanna shoot some hoops?
我不能去  我在练习
I can't go. I'm practicing.
我要参加新游戏节日主持人的试镜
I got an audition to be the host of a new game show.
-酷啊  -太棒了
- Cool! - Great!
如果我能当上主持人
If I get it,
白天我是德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
by day I'll be Dr. Drake Ramoray.
但晚上我是乔伊·崔比安尼
But by night I'll be Joey Tribbiani!
你非常适合这份工作
You'll be perfect for this!
用的都是你的真名耶
That's already your name!
再过几小时就要试镜了 我还没搞懂游戏规则
The auditiors in a couple hours, and I don't understand the game.
你需要帮忙吗
Do you want some help?
真的吗  那真的太棒了
Oh, really? That'd be great.
你们可以当参赛者
Hey, you guys can be the contestants!
帅呆了
Awesome.
输球给初中女生这种事可以等以后再说
Okay, I guess we can lose to junior-high girls some other time.
好吧  我们来玩"晕头转向"
All right. Let's play Bamboozled!
-晕头转向  -对  那个名字很酷吧
- Bamboozled? - Yeah. Isn't that a cool name?
-对  -不
- Yeah! - No!
好吧  第一位参赛者是罗斯·盖勒
All right. Okay. Our first contestant is Ross Geller.
做个简单的自我介绍吧  罗斯
Why don't you tell us a little something about you Ross?
我是古生物学家  我住在纽约
Well, I'm a paleontologist. I live in New York.
我有个儿子叫做本  嗨  本  还有
I have a son, Ben. Hi, Ben! And...
我说了是简单介绍  罗斯
I said, a little bit, Ross.
你呢  钱德勒
Now, how about you, Chandler?
我是个猎头
Joey, I'm a headhunter.
我为卑鄙的第三世界国家
I hook up out-of-work Soviet scientists...
招聘失业的苏联科学家  嗨  拉斯普廷
...with rogue Third World nations. Hi, Rasputin.
太棒了  我们开始吧  钱德勒  你先来
Excellent! Let's play Bamboozled! Chandler, you'll go first.
-哥伦比亚的首都在哪里  -波哥大
- What is the capital of Colombia? - Bogota.
是波格大  但很接近了
It's Bogota, but close enough.
可以把机会让给罗斯
You can either pass your turn to Ross
或选一张魔法机会卡
or pick a Wicked Wango Card.
-魔法机会卡可以做什么  -我应该知道的
- What does a Wicked Wango Card do? - I should know that.
让我看看  请等一下
Let's see. One moment, please...
在这里  魔法机会卡
Here we are. A Wicked Wango Card
能决定你要向上或是向下
determines if you go higher or lower.
什么东西向上或是向下
Higher or lower than what?
这真的是太丢脸了
This is embarrassing!
你不觉得这个游戏很逊吗
Can you believe how lame this is?
抱歉  我想参赛者
I'm sorry. I don't believe contestants
不该相互交谈
are allowed to talk to each other.
我叫脱衣舞男五点到  没问题吧
I told the stripper to be here at 5. That's good, right?
你请脱衣舞男来宝宝欢迎会
You ordered a stripper for the shower?
那太不合适了
That is totally inappropriate.
怎么了  他会打扮成宝宝的样子
Why? He's gonna be dressed as a baby.
嗨  格林太太  我很高兴你赶来了
Oh, hi, Mrs. Green. I'm so glad you could make it.
谢谢你  我们再次表示抱歉
Yeah, thank you so much. And again we're so sorry.
我们真的很过意不去
We could not feel worse about it.
试试看吧
Try.
我女儿在那边
There's my little girl!
-她还在生气  -对  我知道
- She's still mad. - Yeah, I know.
那不是很棒吗  少了一个人跟你闲聊天
Isn't it great? One less person to make small talk with.
菲比  珊卓拉也在生你的气
Phoebe, Sandra's mad at you too.
你心里不纠结吗
It doesn't bother you?
我们道了两次歉  我没有别的办法了
We've apologized twice. I can't do any more than that.
我知道你讨厌别人生你的气
I know you hate it when people are mad at you...
但你得去学着接受
...but you just have to be okay with it.
好吧  我办得到
Okay. I can do that.
我得去给屁股擦点痱子粉
I gotta go powder my ass.
看看你的脸  跟你念高中时一样
Look at that face! Just like when you were in high school.
你要不是我女儿  我还以为你是失足啦啦队长
If I didn't know better, i'd say you were a cheerleader in trouble.
-来吧  我们去喝点茶  -好吧
- Come, let's get some tea. - Okay.
天啊  你看  只剩三星期了
Oh, my! Look at that. Only three weeks to go.
你挑好奶妈了吗
Did you pick a nanny yet?
我不建议让管家兼职
Now I don't want you to use your housekeeper
因为那样她会分心的
'cause it would just split her focus.
事实上  我不打算请奶妈
Actually, I'm not gonna use a nanny.
我也没有管家
And I don't have a housekeeper.
你简直像是山顶洞人
It's like you're a cave person.
瑞秋  你得请个奶妈
Rachel, you must get a nanny.
你不知道带孩子有多累
You don't know how overwhelming this is gonna be.
你小时候我雇用了凯太太
I mean when you were a baby I had full time help, I had Mrs. Kay.
凯太太  对  她人真的很好
Mrs. K! Oh, yeah, she was sweet.
她还教过我西班牙文
She taught me Spanish.
我大概还记得一点
I actually think I remember some of it.
你妈是个疯婆子
Tu madre esta loca.
她真是个好人
Such a sweet woman.
她真的很棒  但我出不起那笔钱
As great as she was, I can't afford that.
瑞秋  我想到一个好点子
Rachel, I just had the greatest idea!
我要搬过去跟你们住
I'm gonna come and live with you!
什么
What? What?
我很高兴我能帮我女儿这个忙
Oh, I'm so happy I'm gonna do this for my little girl.
看看你  你感动得都快哭了
Look at you. You have tears in your eyes.
没错  我是快哭了
Yes, yes, I do.
罗斯  现在是你领先
Ross, you're in the lead.
你要再回答一题
Would you like to take another question
或旋转处罚轮
or spin the Wheel of Mayhem?
今天我转轮子的运气不太好  乔伊
The Wheel has not been my friend tonight, Joey.
我要再回答一题
I'll take another question.
好吧  这题很难  屏住呼吸
Okay. This is gonna be tough. Hold your breath.
没关系  我准备好了
It's okay. I'm ready.
不  哥们  在你回答问题之前
No dude, you gotta hold your breath
要一直屏住呼吸
until you're ready to answer the question.
这是游戏规则
This is part of the game.
这太可笑了  他没法屏住...
This is ridiculous! He's not gonna hold his...
好吧  如果你患有这种恐惧症
Okay. What do you have a fear of
那你害怕的是什么  恐...
if you suffer from this phobia? Triska...
天啊  那个词真长  恐...
Holy cow. That's a big word. Trisk...
看看这个词  钱德勒  这该怎么念
Seriously, look at this. Chandler, how do you say that?
-让我看看  -就是这个词
- Let me see that. - This one right here.
-恐十三症  -害怕薄脆饼干
- Triskaidekaphobia. - Fear of Triscuits!
-不  是害怕数字十三  -害怕薄脆饼干
- No! No. Fear of the number 13. - Fear of Triscuits?
这有可能  饼干的边缘很锋利的
It's possible. They have really sharp edges.
钱德勒  轮到你了
Alright, Chandler, you're up.
等等  我可以用天使通行证换一次答题机会
Wait a minute. I'm entitled to use my Angel Pass for a free turn.
这个游戏真的很没有道理
This game makes no sense!
你生气是因为你要输了
You're upset because you're losing.
少来了  罗斯  我觉得我们都是失败者
Oh, come on, Ross. I think we're all losers here.
好  钱德勒
Alright, Chandler.
你可以选旋转轮子或挑一张搜索卡
You can either spin the Wheel or pick a Google Card.
让我想想
Let me think, let me think.
我不在乎
Oh, I don't care.
你非选不可  宾先生
You must choose, Mr. Bing.
那还是没有差别
Either. It makes no difference.
快选吧  混蛋
Choose, you jackass.
-我要抽卡片  -好的  你抽到了贪心卡
- I'll take a card. - Okay, you picked the Gimme Card!
-你拿到了罗斯所有的分数  -什么
- You get all of Ross' points! - What?
这个游戏开始好玩起来了
This game is kind of fun!
你不觉得你拿到我的分数太疯狂了...
You don't think it's a little crazy that you get all my points...
参赛者不该相互交谈的
I don't think the contestants aren't supposed to speak to each other.
-你为什么要邀请我妈来  -什么
- Why did you invite my mother? - What?
她要搬过来跟我和罗斯住
She wants to move in with me and Ross
以便帮忙照顾宝宝
to help take care of the baby.
-多久  -八星期
- For how long? - Eight weeks.
我爱我妈
I love my mother,
但是跟她一起吃长午餐就是种折磨
but, my God, a long lunch with her is taxing.
如果她想跟我住  我会觉得很荣幸
I personally would be honored if she wanted to live with me.
她又听不到你拍马屁
She can't hear you.
我该怎么样
What am I gonna do?
如果不希望她搬过去  你该直说
If you don't want your mother to move in with you, just tell her.
你说得对  我就快生了
You're right. You're right. I'm about to have a baby.
我可以说我不希望她
I can tell my mother that I don't want her
睡在我家沙发上
to just be sleeping on my couch!
她会睡在我床上 绝不能让那种事发生
She'll wanna sleep in my bed with me. This can't happen.
没错
That's right. That is right.
你去告诉她
You go over there and tell her
你不希望她搬过去跟你们住
you don't want her to live with you.
-一定要坚持立场  -好
- Do not take no for an answer. - Okay.
这简直太棒了  现在她会生瑞秋的气
This is great! Now she's gonna be mad at Rachel!
我要趁虚而入
And I'm just gonna swoop in there
当她的乖女儿讨好她
and be like the daughter she never had.
我对钱德勒又产生了新的敬意
I have new respect for Chandler.
好了  大伙们  该来拆礼物了
All right, everybody! It's time to open the presents!
对  瑞秋要拆的第一样礼物...
Yes! I think the first gift that Rachel opens...
应该是外婆送的礼物
...should be from the grandmother of the baby.
因为你是这里最重要的人
Because you're the most important person in this room!
也是全世界最重要的人
And in the world!
我没有准备礼物
I don't have a gift
因为我直到最后时刻才受到邀请
because I wasn't invited until the last minute.
但非常谢谢你  亲爱的
But thank you so much, dear,
让大家都注意到这一点
for bringing that to everybody's attention.
你们这些不太重要的人呢
How about you less important people?
我们来拆你们的礼物吧
Let's open your presents!
你没准备礼物也没关系
It's okay that you didn't get me a gift.
但我也算是送了你一样礼物
I kind of did.
我要跟你同住八个星期
Me! Eight weeks of me.
好吧  妈  事实上我可以自己照顾宝宝
Okay. See, Mom, the truth is, I can do this on my own.
宝贝  我知道你会是个好妈妈
Sweet heart, I know you're gonna be a terrific mom.
但我觉得一开始你还是需要有人帮忙
I just think you need a little help, especially at the beginning.
我知道自己在做什么  我应付得来
But mom, I really know what I'm doing. I can handle this.
真的吗  还记得亮亮吗
Really? Remember Twinkles?
他是只仓鼠  我又不会拿吸尘器吸我的宝宝
He was a hamster. I'm not gonna vacuum up my baby!
快来吧  瑞秋  拆礼物的时间到了
Okay, come on, Rach. It's present time!
你是这个派对的主角
You're the glue holding this party together.
现在这个派对也快毁了
It's kind of falling apart here.
-你看  -哇
- Oh, look! - Wow!
这是你同事送的
This is from your friends at work.
天啊  哇
Oh, my gosh! Oh, wow!
我知道这是什么
Oh, I know what this is.
等一下
Wait a minute.
不可能啊
That can't be right.
这是宝宝啤酒机吗
Is that a beer bong for a baby?
女儿  那是挤奶器
Darling, that's a breast pump.
我说过我猜完了吗
Did I say I was done guessing?
好吧  谢谢
Okay, thank you for that.
哇  这是什么
Oh, wow! What's this?
-是尿布精灵  -是用来放干净尿布的
- It's a Diaper Genie. - It dispenses clean diapers!
那是放脏尿布的
No. It's where you put dirty ones.
真恶心  为什么不直接把脏尿布
That's gross. Why don't you take it outside
丢在外面的垃圾桶里
and throw it in a dumpster?
你每天要丢十次吗
You're gonna do that 10 times a day?
什么  宝宝一天可以拉十次
What, it goes 10 times a day?
难道我们给她喂的是印度食物吗
Are we feeding this baby Indian food?
不  宝宝都是那样的
No, dear. That's what babies do.
瑞秋  听你妈妈的话  她非常聪明
Rachel, listen to your mother. She is very smart.
再说  你去倒垃圾的时候
Plus, what are you planning on doing with the baby
你的宝宝该怎么办
while you're trotting out to the garbage ten times a day?
我不知道  把她放在尿布桌上
I don't know, I'd leave it on the changing table?
怎么  我做错了什么
What? What did I do? What did I do?
你不能丢下宝宝一个人
You can't leave a baby alone.
我当然知道
Of course, I know that!
千万不能丢下宝宝一个人
Of course you never leave a baby alone.
那样... 她会很不安全
It would... She wouldn't be safe.
她跟我这个菜鸟妈妈在一起也会不安全
Not as safe as she would be with me, the baby dummy.
这样吧
You know what?
现在拆礼物让我有点不知所措
Opening the presents is a little overwhelming right now.
我待会再把礼物都拆开
So I think I'm gonna maybe open them all a little bit later.
谢谢你们赶来  还送了礼物...
But thank you for coming, and for these beautiful gifts...
这个篮子很漂亮
...and this basket is beautiful.
那其实是个摇篮
It's actually a bassinet.
好吧  妈妈  别离开我
Okay, Mommy, don't ever leave me.
这是约翰·休斯顿哪部电影里的台词
In what John Houston film would you hear this line,
"警徽  我们不需要臭警徽"
"Badges? We don't need no stinking badges!"
《碧血金沙》
Treasure of the Sierra Madre!
答对了  倒念还能加分
Correct! There's a possible backwards bonus!
-沙金血碧  -对
- Madre Sierra the of Treasure! - Yes!
我要爬上机会梯到金泥屋去
I'd like to go up the Ladder of Chance to the Golden Mud Hut, please!
-明智的选择  几阶  -六阶
- Wise choice. How many rungs? - Six!
-那个声音只代表一种东西  -饥饿的猴子
- That noise can only mean one thing. - Hungry Monkey!
-我要魔法机会卡  -好
- I'd like a Wicked Wango Card. - Okay.
这是声音题
It's an audio question.
说出这出电视剧的主题曲
Name this television theme song:
天啊  我知道  让我想一想
Oh, my God. I know this. Give me a second.
-去跟时间乌龟说吧  -闭嘴
- Tell it to the Time Turtle! - Shut up!
-《太空仙女恋》  -答对了  你再度领先
- "I Dream of Jeannie"! - Yes! Back in the lead!
我要转轮子
I'd like to spin the Wheel.
快点
Oh, come on!
超级快速答题回合
Super Speedy Speed Round.
-跳跃有加分吗  -当然
- Is there a Hopping Bonus? - Of course.
-谁发明了双焦点透镜  -本·富兰克林
- Who invented bifocals? - Ben Franklin!
答对了  哪位君王统治英国最久
Correct. Which monarch ruled Great Britain the longest?
-维多莉亚女王  -再次正确
- Queen Victoria! - Correct again.
但你忘了换题时要换腿跳
But you forgot to switch legs between questions.
所以跳跃动作不加分
So, no Hopping Bonus!
每次都这样
Every time!
-对  现在轮到钱德勒了  -我要搜索卡
- Yeah. Now over to Chandler. - I'd like a Google Card.
-你确定吗  -对  不  搜索卡
- Are you sure? - Yes! No! Google!
天啊  恭喜你  罗斯  因为钱德勒...
Oh, my God! Congratulations, Ross! Because, Chandler...
-你已经出局了  -不
- you've been Bamboozled! - No!
-对  -这是我玩过最棒的游戏
- Yes! - This is the best game ever!
只要我有需要  你就会留下来吗
So you'll stay as long as I need you?
当然了
Of course, I am.
妈  我发誓我不是白痴
Mom, I swear I'm not an idiot.
我看了各种有关怀孕跟生产的书
I read all kind of books on pregnancy and giving birth.
但我没想到要去看
But I just didn't think to read the part
带孩子方面的书
about what to do when the baby comes.
可现在呢  宝宝就快要出生了
And-and then guess what? The baby's coming...
我却不知道该怎么办
...and I don't know what to do.
我可以吐在尿布精灵里吗
Oh, can I throw up in my Diaper Genie?
甜心  你会没事的
Sweetie, you're gonna be fine.
-你要去哪里  -我得上洗手间
- Where you going? - I'm going to the bathroom.
别担心  一切都会没事的
Now, don't worry. Everything's gonna be okay.
确实会没事的
It is gonna be okay!
这值得一试
Worth a shot.
你干嘛满脸通红全身是汗
Hey! Why are you all red and sweaty?
我刚刚干掉了钱德勒
I just Bamboozled Chandler!
我对他没有不轨行为
Which is not a sexual thing.
欢迎会这么快就结束了
Well, that was a quick shower.
那是因为你没参加
Not if you were here.
看来我们收到不少礼物
Looks like we got a lot of good stuff.
没错  我妈给了我们最棒的礼物
We did, but my mom got us the greatest gift of all.
培乐多理发师玩具组
A Play-Doh Barbershop?
不是  她要搬过来跟我们住八星期
No. She's going to live with us for eight weeks.
什么
What?
对  她要帮我们照顾宝宝
Yes! She's gonna help us take care of the baby!
你不是认真的吧
You're not serious!
她是个好人
She's a very nice woman,
但我们无法忍受她八个星期
but there's no way we can take eight weeks of her.
-她会把我们逼疯  -嗨  罗斯
- She'll drive us totally crazy... - Hi, Ross!
嘿  室友
Hey, roomie!
乔伊  我是雷  本节日的制作人
Hey, Joey, I'm Ray. I'm the producer of the show.
很荣幸能见到你  雷
It's a pleasure to meet you, Ray.
他们是唐肯跟艾玲  他们会帮你试镜
This is Duncan and Erin. They're gonna help with the audition.
现在开拍吧
So uh, let's get the camera rolling.
-好的  雷  -你准备好了就开始
- Right, Ray. - Whenever you're ready.
大家好  我是乔伊·崔比安尼
Hello. I'm Joey Tribbiani.
我们来玩晕头转向吧
Let's play Bamboozled!
艾玲  你先来作答
Erin, you get the first question.
在曲棍球史上  谁被称为是"伟人"
In hockey, who is known as "The Great One"?
-葛瑞斯基  -答对了
- Gretzky. - Correct!
你要挑魔法机会卡
Now, would you like to pick a Wicked Wango Card
还是旋转处罚轮
or spin the Wheel of Mayhem?
你的经纪人没把改过的游戏规则给你吗
Joey, didn't your agents give you the revised rules?
我们把那些东西都删掉了 没有轮子或机会卡
We've eliminated all that. No wheel. No cards.
为什么
Why?
之前的游戏太复杂了
The game was too complicated
调查显示观众无法理解
and research showed people didn't follow it.
哪里复杂了
Well what's complicated?
转处罚轮  上机会梯
You spin the Wheel of Mayhem to go up the Ladder of Chance...
穿越彩虹环  经过泥屋
You go past the Mud Hut through the Rainbow Ring
找到金猴
to the Golden Monkey.
拉它的尾巴就能到天堂池
You yank his tail, and you're in Paradise Pond!
对  那些都删掉了
Yeah. All that's gone.
现在这只是个简单的问答游戏
It's basically just a simple question-and-answer game now.
那有什么好玩的呢
Well, what's fun about that?
你要我主持这个无聊的游戏
You expect me to host a boring game
就只是几个人站在那里傻傻地回答问题
that's just people standing around answering questions?
会有比基尼女郎举得分板
Well, there'll be women in bikinis holding up the scores.
我们来玩晕头转向吧
Let's play Bamboozled!
你买的那些恐龙小玩意  罗斯
Oh, and all those dinosaur knickknacks you have, Ross,
我觉得还是放在车库里比较合适
I thought they might be more at home in the garage.
我们没有车库
Well, we don't have a garage.
我说车库吗  我是说垃圾桶
Did I say garage? I meant garbage.
你知道吗  格林太太
You know what, Mrs. Green?
你不一定要跟我们住在一起
Maybe it's not absolutely vital that you live with us.
瑞秋需要人帮忙带孩子
Well, Rachel needs help with the baby.
真的  我什么都不会
I do. I really do. I don't know anything.
我相信那不是真的
I'm sure that's not true.
是吗  菲比  莫妮卡  我会带孩子吗
Oh, no? Pheebs, Monica, do I know anything about babies?
-啥都不会  -令人发指
- No. Not a thing. - It's frightening.
就算她不会  但是我会
Even if she doesn't know anything, I do.
我有个儿子  他妈妈跟我没有住在一起
I have a son. His mother and I didn't live together.
他跟我一起住时  我都是自己照顾他
When he was with me, I took care of him all the time, by myself.
-没错  你还有一个孩子  -对
- That's true. You do have another child. - Yeah.
跟另一个女人生的
With another woman.
你没有自制力吗  罗斯
Have you no control, Ross?
那是另一个问题
That's a different issue.
重点是宝宝出生后
The point is, when the baby comes,
我会帮忙喂她吃饭
I will be there to feed her...
帮她洗澡  换尿布
...and bathe her and change her.
更重要的是  我愿意照顾她
And more than that, I want to do all those things.
-那你们真的不需要我搬过去  -对
- You don't need me to live with you. - Yes!
对  我会想念你的
Yes. You're gonna be so missed.
-你会是个好爸爸  -你会是个好外婆
- You'll be a great father. - You'll be a wonderful grandma.
喂  我还是不知道我该做什么
Hello? I still don't know what the hell I'm doing!
新手妈妈都会有那种感觉
Every first-time mother feels that way.
你可以慢慢学
You're gonna pick it up.
你可以的   你刚到纽约来的时候
Hey, you will. Look, when you first came to the city...
你是个被宠坏的无助小女孩
...you were this spoiled, helpless little girl
只会用爸爸的信用卡  记得吗
who still used Daddy's credit cards, remember?
我希望你下面的话有点建设性
I hope you're going somewhere with this.
看看你  你现在是个大主管了
Look at you. You're this big executive.
你比自己想象中能干多了
You are much more capable than you give yourself credit for.
我相信你会是个好妈妈
I have no doubt you're gonna be an incredible mother.
-真的吗  -没错
- Really? - I'm telling you.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧  我得走了
All right, you two. I'm gonna get going.
不  亲爱的  别送了
No, sweetheart, you stay put.
我自己出去
I'll let myself out.
就当我没来过  我差点真的来不了
It's like I'm not here. Which I almost wasn't.
你真的太幽默了
You're just so funny. You're so funny.
我到底该怎么办
What do I do?
没什么  你跟她道过很多次歉了
Nothing. You have apologized to her, like, a million times.
结果她对你的态度还是一样恶劣
And she's been nothing but terrible to you.
别忘了  你刚刚帮她女儿
And don't forget, you just threw her daughter
办了个稍显无聊的温馨欢迎会
a lovely, albeit slightly boring, shower.
她甚至都没有谢谢你
And she hasn't even thanked you for it.
你说得对
You know what? You're right.
你有什么话想跟她说  直说无妨
If you wanna say anything to her, tell her off.
真的吗
Really?
好吧  我会的
Okay, I will.
格林太太
Mrs. Green?
不跟主人道别就离开派对是很无礼的
It is rude to leave a party without saying goodbye to the host.
如果有人跟你道歉
And also, when someone apologizes to you,
得体的做法是接受道歉
the decent thing to do is to accept it.
我对你的所作所为并非故意
Because what I did to you, it wasn't on purpose!
但你对我的态度太恶毒了
But what you're doing to me now is plain spiteful.
-恶毒  -没错
- Spiteful? - That's right.
你该好好去照镜子了  小姑娘
Maybe it's time you took a good, hard look in the mirror, young lady!
老太婆
Old lady!
女士
Lady!
别说了
Wrap it up. Wrap it up. Wrap it up.
只要你准备好跟我道歉  我会原谅你的
So whenever you're ready to apologize to me, I will forgive you.
再见
Good day.
我的腿没有感觉了
I can't feel my legs!
你真的太棒了  我以你为荣
You were fantastic! I'm so proud of you.
-是吗  我也以自己为荣  -你应该的
- Yeah? I'm proud of me too. - You should be.
-你能帮我拿杯饮料吗  -没问题
- Could you get me something to drink? - You got it!
格林太太  我真的很抱歉
Mrs. Green? Okay, I'm really sorry!
对不起  如果你...
I apologize. If you...
好吧  我咬到舌头了
Okay! I bit my tongue!
但我真的很抱歉
But I'm still really sorry!
-好吧  我准备好了  -你确定
- Okay, I'm ready. - You sure?
对  我看过书  把一切都搞清楚了
Yes. I've done my studying, and I really know my stuff.
好吧
All right, then.
瑞秋·格林 我们来玩晕头转向
Rachel Green, let's play Bamboozled!
你该如何测试宝宝洗澡水的温度
How do you test the temperature of the baby's bath water?
-用手肘去试  -非常好
- Put your elbow in it. - Excellent!
如何哄宝宝小睡
How do you put a baby down for a nap?
喂饱她  换尿布  仰卧  被子盖紧
Full, dry, on its back, no loose covers.
答对了
That's correct!
这题是声音题
This is an audio question.
宝宝发出这种声音时你该怎么办
What do you do when a baby makes this sound:
检查她是尿湿或饿了  帮她拍背
Check if it's wet, check if it's hungry, burp it!
太棒了
Excellent! Excellent!
你要再回答一题或抽魔法机会卡
Now do you want another question or a Wicked Wango Card?
-我要抽卡  -对不起
- A card! A card! I pick a card! - Oh, I'm sorry.
你出局了 你会是个糟糕的妈妈
You've been Bamboozled! You're gonna be a terrible mother!
我忘记我们这么做的初衷是什么了
I've lost sight of why we're doing this!